http://www.schoolexpress.com/legal.php

Welcome to SchoolExpress.
We offer numerous FREE items -
19,000+ worksheets, create worksheets, funtime games, online math, and more.
Legal Notice
Under no circumstances may any of the SchoolExpress webpages be displayed within a frame on another website. We are very strict about this policy and will take legal action against any website that displays any of the pages of the SchoolExpress website within a frame on another website.
All materials on the SchoolExpress web pages are copyrighted. They may not be added to any other server without written permission from Comp Ed, Inc.
All the worksheets on the SchoolExpress website are copyrighted.
Teachers, homeschooling families, and parents may print as many copies of each worksheet as needed for their students/children.
Copies of each worksheet may be made on a copy machine.
These copies may be distributed to students in school classrooms or for home use.
The worksheets may not be re-distributed or stored on any other servers. Our worksheets may be listed with the descriptions on other websites. Links for downloading must take the user to our site. We do not allow other websites to let users download directly from that site. All downloads must come through our website.
info@schoolexpress.com
to request further information.
If you have any questions about the U.S. copyright laws click here.
United States Coyright Laws
Privacy Statement
SchoolExpress Committment:
SchoolExpress is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its online visitors. We are sensitive to concerns about children's personal information and safety.
We encourage visitors to read and understand our privacy statement. This statement may be updated to address any new issues.
Use of our site by you shall be deemed to constitute acceptance by you of this statement or any revise statement.
Newsletter Subscribers:
We do not sell, rent or otherwise disclose subscribers' email addresses to third parties. Information on how to unsubscribe to our mailing list is included in every mailing we do.
SchoolExpress collects information in various ways. a.
When you place an order through our online store
you will provide your name, address, phone number, and email address.
This information is only used for processing your order and referring to it at a later time if there is a question about your order.b.	When you subscribe to our weekly newsletter your email address is stored in the newsletter database.
This is only used for sending our newsletters.c.
Google analytics provides us data on traffic statistics.
This is non-personally identifiable information.
This is anonymous visitor data.
It does not collect personal information such as names, ages, phone numbers, addresses or e-mail addresses.
Chidren's Privacy - COPPA Compliant:1.
Children use the Funtime area of the SchoolExpress website.a.
SchoolExpress does not knowingly collect any information from children.
Please instruct your children to never give out their real names, addresses, or phone numbers without permission when using the Internet.
b.
SchoolExpress is in compliance with COPPA (the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act).SchoolExpress adheres to the following policies:
a.
We will NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.
b.
We will NOT knowingly provide any direct link to websites that are unsuitable for children or teens.
Placing An Order:
When you place an order on the Comp Ed, Inc. website you can be assured that your information is only used for the purpose to complete your order or to reference your order when you have a question.
IP Addresses:
Every computer or network on the Internet has a unique, identifying number known as an IP address. SchoolExpress does collect IP addresses.
When a visitor accesses a page from our site, our host server logs the visitor's IP address.
Cookies:"Cookies" are commonly used in the Internet industry. They are small text files written to your computer. They save your preferences while you are visiting websites.
The information tracked with cookies is anonymous and is not used to lead back to, any particular visitor.
When clicking through on an ad on any of the web pages you may get cookies from our advertisers or sponsors.
SchoolExpress does not control these cookies.
Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you may change the settings so that your browser can refuse cookies. If you choose to refuse cookies, some features on SchoolExpress site, such as what features are presented may not function properly on your computer.
Our Advertisers:
SchoolExpress offers ad space for other companies.
When you click on an ad to view the advertiser's site please read their privacy policy.
We do not have control over the advertiser's policies.a.
Google, as and ad vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the SchoolExpress site.b.
Google uses the DART cookie to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our pages and other sites on the Internet.c.
As a site user you may learn more here or opt out of the use of the DART cookie here
Please contact us if you have further concerns about your privacy. Protecting the privacy of our visitors is important to us.
All our Thematic Units and Subject eWorkbooks are located on the SchoolExpress TeacherSherpa page here!
Below are quick links to all the Thematic Units and Subject eWorkbooks on the SchoolExpress TeacherSherpa page.
Industrial Rev.
Thank you for using the SchoolExpress website!
SchoolExpress has a variety of educational materials.
We have lots of FREE items..
Teachers, homeschooling families, parents, children, and grandparents use our site.
We have received hundreds of emails from our community of site users.
Read many of the comments here.
© 2015 Comp Ed, Inc. Updated weekly.
